occourts.org 2019-05-09

# The Superior Court of California - County of Orange

#### WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

This policy covers how OCSC treats personal information that it receives, including information related to your past use of certain Court services. Personal information is information about you that is uniquely identifiable such as your name, residential address, email address, or phone number.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTED AND USE GENERAL

OCSC retains personal information when you use certain OCSC online applications. For example, when you use certain Court online services we may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, and occupation. When you input this information the Court may retain it in order to assist you in future transaction and to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for services, improve our services, or to contact you in order to alert to you an impending court appearance or some other issue that we feel may be important to your Court-related matter.

#### CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We strictly limit access to personal information about you to those employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide assistance to you. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

**We do create individual profiles with the information you provide. We do not give it to any other public or private organization for commercial purposes or otherwise**. There is one exception to this policy: if you communicate a threat or a message that describes or promotes unlawful activity, the Court will share it with law enforcement. 

The Court may use a 3rd party to collect website usage statistics. We do not share this information with outside agencies. 

#### IF YOU E-MAIL THE COURT

DO NOT use e-mails to this website for inquiries or information about specific cases. E-mails sent to this address shown below will not be reviewed on a regular basis, if ever. Use this method of communication at your own risk. E-mail links within specific applications that you subscribe to will adhere to their own information retention and tracking policy as described within their own ‘terms of use’. It is recommended that these links be used for any questions regarding that particular application. 

#### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

This site contains links to other websites. The Orange County Superior Court is not responsible for the practices or contents of these websites.

#### NO SUBSTITUTE FOR LEGAL ADVICE

No warranty of any kind, expressed or implied is made with respect to any information or third party sites accessed through this page. Further, this website is not a substitute for legal advice. Much of the information provided by this website is subject to change, so you should verify the accuracy and current status of any information published herein before relying upon it.

#### CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or our Website, you may contact us via the email links for Feedback and Webmaster at the bottom of this page. Please do not, however, ask for legal advice or specific information on a case.

#### OUR POSTAL ADDRESS IS:

700 Civic Center Drive West  
Santa Ana, CA 92701
